Subtitles by champdgr8
Get to it.
♪ Black eyes open wide
It's time to testify
♪ There is no room for lies
And everyone's waiting for you
♪ Then I'm gone
Sitting by the phone
♪ And I'm all alone
By the wayside
♪ And I'm gone
Sitting by the phone
♪ And I'm all alone
By the wayside ♪
Jackson! No!
Roger.
You're a wonderful man. yes.
and you're a great lawyer.
We're just not meant
to be together.
No. I don't wanna marry you!
Are you crazy?
The hell's the matter
with you?
Roger. we're done.
Oh. my God.
Fuck! God!
Fucking men!
Did he cry?
Yeah. he cried. He laughed.
He yelled at me.
- You know. whatever.
- You broke his heart. Mama.
I did the right thing.
- Ally. garbage!
- It just wasn't right... Oh. hey. Bryan.
Can you get somebody else
to do it for me?
- You have to let her shine!
- It's your fucking turn!
- Oh. my God!
- Who the fuck
- is he talking to?
- Okay. I'll see you upstairs.
Come on. Bryan!
She's performing tonight!
Here we go. Taking out
the trash. Wipe your mouth.
I'll let you go early.
but you gotta finish your job.
Well. you gotta keep
your mouth clean. Okay?
♪ When all the world
is a hopeless jumble
♪ And the raindrops
tumble all around
♪ Heaven opens a magic lane
♪ When all the clouds
darken up the skyway
♪ There's a rainbow highway
to be found ♪
Where the fuck are we?
We are east of the city.
Is there any more?
No. No. sorry. Jack.
And it's about an hour-forty
with traffic
till we get there.
- Wait. really?
- Yeah.
I think we can find something
around here.
No. I'll find something.
I'll find something.
How's your kid?
How old is he now?
- He is 17.
- Fuck me.
And he got a scholarship
to play baseball
in college already. man.
Wow. that's great.
I'm proud of him.
My little guy is
not so little anymore.
I don't wanna go home.
Wish I could find you a spot.
Sorry. Jack.
I don't know this area.
Would you make a right here?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
All right.
Here we go.
That looks like a fucking bar.
- Here?
- What's that say? "Bleu Bleu."
Here. let me just try this.
Oh. shit!
Wait. wait.
My man. my man. I...
Aren't you that...
- Aren't you. like...
- This is a bar. right?
Yeah. but I don't know
if this is your kind of place.
- They got alcohol?
- Well. yeah. but...
Oh.
it's my kind of place.
Oh. shit! This is crazy!
- How are you doin'. papo?
- How am I doin'?
I'm doin' all right
if I can get a fucking drink.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Oh. my gosh!
Oh. yeah. There's the bar.
This is my home girl.
Giselle de la Isma.
Hey. how you doin'? Hey.
Oh. yeah. That's Jack.
That's Jack.
♪ Oh. yeah. yeah. at last
Excuse me. papo!
Can we get this man
anything he wants. please?
Can I get a gin on the rocks
with a twist. please?
♪ The skies above are blue ♪
Papo. wow.
Oh. my gosh.
I'm freaking out right now.
Hey. is this a drag bar?
Yeah. papo. Yeah. yeah.
But look.
we do this every Friday night.
Yo. it's crazy.
It's so lit. though.
I thought maybe I was in some
sort of hallucinogenic state.
- My honor. or something...
- No. no. no. All are welcome.
- A dress or something.
- All are welcome.
You gonna have something?
Here. let me get you a drink.
Okay. Yeah. wow.
You better get out
there and kill 'em tonight.
All you ladies
kill it tonight. okay?
- I'm ready.
- I always do!
Ladies. make sure you've
turned in your music already.
Don't make me have
to come get you tonight.
This is a professional show.
Right.
Oh. yes! You stayed!
That's good.
That's good. I like it.
Everything good? You good?
Yeah. I was just
talking to Nicki.
You know Nicki?
Hello. Nicki.
How you doin'. baby?
She's telling me her
life story. Fascinating.
My home girl's
about to perform.
And y'all know her very well
because she used to work here
as a server. But tonight.
the only thing she's serving
are some fabulous.
French live vocals.
Is she really singing. though.
or is it one of
those karaoke things?
No. no. no.
She's really singing. papo.
I promise you.
she's really singing.
- Okay.
- Watch this. Watch.
Would anybody
like some French tips tonight?
Yes. baby! Yes. baby!
Oh. fuck.
- Oh. papo. you crying?
- A little bit.
You have to meet her.
- What's that?
- You have to meet her!
- Oh. no. I can't meet her.
- Yes! Come on.
Donte. you got a rag.
honey? Thank you.
Miss Ally. Mama.
now you done sang in French
tonight. you gonna pick
something else next week?
I don't know.
Look there.
she's doing languages now.
- Do Moroccan.
- No!
This is my friend.
Jackson Maine.
Hey.
- This is Jackson Maine.
- Hey.
- How are you? Hey.
- Hey! Oh. my God!
Right?
This is my friend. Ally.
- Oh. my God! Hi.
- Hi. Hey.
I thought that might be you.
- What'd you say?
- "I thought
- "that might be you."
- That's me.
Thank you! You wanna sit down?
No! You've been
on your feet all night.
No! You're our guest.
you're our guest.
- You sure you don't mind?
- A little drink?
I'm here watching the show.
watching you guys.
- Word!
- Yeah. yeah.
- Will you sign my boob?
- Sure.
- Yeah. I can do that.
- Oh. my God!
Give me a sharpie!
It's BYOB around here.
- Yeah. is that right?
- "Bring your own boobs."
Oh. God!
Those aren't really her boobs?
Wow!
So why are you in here. hon?
- Sorry?
- What brings you here?
Oh. I was playing right around
here tonight. I'm a musician.
How'd your show go?
Uh... I think
it went all right.
- Okay. here we go. All right.
- Thank you!
- That's all right?
- Oh. my.
Which one should I do?
- Do 'em both! I don't care!
- Select!
Why don't I
just do it across?
Bitch. Jackson Maine!
- I'll just...
- Oh. my!
She will stop
at nothing.
- You gotta blow on it!
- I did it pretty big. Oh.
Oh. you got it. Okay.
Thank you so much!
You all gotta go home.
but you know the phrase.
You gotta get the hell
up outta here!
'Cause tonight. I'm not losing
my virginity
or my liquor license
over you bitches. so pack up!
- That's right!
- That's enough cocktails!
Clear it out!
Hello. goodbye. Roger.
Have fun!
Bring the drinks on out!
Do you do that often?
- Do what?
- The show.
Yeah. yeah. The girls
are so nice to me here.
I mean.
they would never normally
let a girl sing at
one of these shows.
but they've always
loved my voice.
They used to beg me to sing.
It's an honor. really. I get
to be one of the gay girls.
Is that your real eyebrow?
Um... No. No.
I make it out of tape.
- Oh. so it's stuck on?
- Mmm-hmm.
Can I try to take it off?
Uh... Yeah. sure.
It's incredible
what they do.
Look at that.
Oh! Yep. There it is.
I should
put her down somewhere.
Okay.
There we go.
Why're you covering your eye?
Oh. just 'cause I don't have
my eyebrow on anymore.
Oh. no. no. The whole point is
I can see your face.
Yeah. there we go.
Why did you come back here?
Your friend brought me
back here. I'm glad he did.
Can I buy you a drink?
Oh.
I gotta change.
and I got paint in my hair.
- That's not your real hair?
- My eyebrows are...
No. my hair is
like your color.
- Oh. okay.
- But I paint it with this
makeup.
I'd love to see
what that looks like.
I'll wait for you.
Um...
Yeah. okay. Sure.
Yeah. if you wanna wait. I'll
come have a drink with you.
Sure.
Bitch. can you get down
off that stage
and come help me
close this bar. please?
Don't talk to me like that
in that bus driver wig. girl.
Oh. I know you did not.
What. you have a street
appointment tonight. sister?
Excuse me!
Mr. Maine. would you mind?
Uh... What do you
want me to do?
Just come play
a little song for me.
I don't know.
Can you leave
the man alone. please?
I showed you mine. you show
me yours. Come on.
He already signed your tits.
honey. Say. "No. sir."
Show off for me a little bit.
I'll only do it because
you already performed.
You're so nice.
Thank you.
Lord. the man is here
for Ally. Not for you. sister.
She's nice. Yeah.
Isn't it cute?
Little arts and crafts.
- Yeah. and light.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Did you do this yourself?
- Yeah. all me.
Well. it's great.
Does this mic work?
Oh. yeah. Fuck. all right.
What do you want me to play?
I don't care. just look at me
while you do it.
Oh. Lord!
Somebody kill me now.
Let me see what I can...
All right.
♪ Maybe it's time
to let the old ways die
♪ It takes a lot
to change a man
♪ Hell. it takes a lot to try
♪ Maybe it's time
to let the old ways die
♪ Nobody knows
what waits for the dead
♪ Some folks just believe
In the things they've heard
♪ And the things they've read
♪ Nobody knows
what waits for the dead
♪ I'm glad I can't go back
to where I came from
♪ I'm glad those days are gone
Gone for good
♪ If I could take spirits
♪ From my past
and bring 'em here
♪ You know I would
You know I would ♪
You're ready?
- You know I would!
- Okay.
- It's a cop bar.
- Cops?
Yeah. that's why
they serve all night long.
Can I ask you
a personal question?
Sure.
Do you write songs
or anything?
I don't sing my own songs.
Thank you.
Why?
I just don't feel comfortable.
Why wouldn't you
feel comfortable?
Um...
Well. 'cause almost
every single person
that I've come in contact with
in the music industry
has told me
that my nose is too big
and that I won't make it.
- Your nose is too big?
- Yeah.
Your nose is beautiful.
Are you showing me
your nose right now?
- Yeah.
- You don't have to show it
to me. I've been
looking at it all night.
Oh. come on. No. you're not.
I'm gonna be thinking about
your nose for a very long
- time. I'm not full of shit.
- You're full of shit.
- Yeah. you are. Yeah. you're full of shit.
- I'm telling you the truth.
- Can I touch your nose?
- Oh. my gosh!
Let me just touch it
for a second.
You're very lucky.
- Oh. really? Yeah. not really.
- Mmm-hmm.
My nose has not made me lucky.
I could've had
maybe a hit song
if it wasn't for my nose.
That's fucking bullshit.
Yeah. No. it's not bullshit
because you go
into these rooms.
and there's all these
fucking men in there.
and they're
just staring at you.
listening to your record.
going.
"Oh. you sound great.
but you don't look so great."
You know. I had a thing
when I was little.
I was born with this thing
in my ear. couldn't hear.
What do I wind up being?
A singer. so you never know.
Look. talent comes everywhere.
Everybody's talented.
Bet you fucking everybody
in this bar is talented
in one thing or another.
but having something to say
and the way to say it
so people listen to it.
that's a whole other bag.
And unless you get out there
and you try to do it.
you'll never know.
That's just the truth.
If there's one reason
we're supposed to be here.
it's to say something
so people wanna hear it.
Don't you understand
what I'm trying to tell you?
Yeah. I do.
I don't like it.
but I understand it.
Oh. I think
you like it a little bit.
I think I'm getting through
a little bit. I can see it.
No. you can't.
It's a good thing we met.
- Yeah.
- For both of us.
- Trust me.
- I don't know what is going on.
- Honestly. what...
- Who does?
I'm in a cop bar. with
Jackson Maine. It's. like...
Jackson Maine!
I'm gonna wake up in a minute.
That's the thing
about when you get famous.
people start saying
your full name.
- Well. what do you want...
- Just "Jack."
Oh. speaking of...
Come on.
- What?
- Did you put that on?
You put that on. When did you
even go to the jukebox?
Oh. God!
I hear that song. and I just
wanna turn it the fuck off.
Jack Maine!
I fucked
that fucking song up so bad.
- No! What? Come on.
- Oh. my God!
Hey. I know that
we're not supposed to do this.
I know that we're not supposed
to come and bother you.
- You come here every night.
- That's all right.
You got your camera on you?
'Cause I don't have my camera.
Excuse me. one sec.
My ex-girlfriend was
fucking this guy.
- Right. Okay.
- Who looks like you.
- that's what she said.
- Shut the hell up.
But I gotta take
a picture of you
because I gotta send it to her
because I'm gonna show her
that you look
nothing fucking like
that fucking guy.
Jack. I'm sorry.
Maybe that'll help her out.
Will that help you out?
Will that make you happy?
Why don't we take
the fucking picture?
You want someone
to take the picture?
- Hey. no. no. It's okay.
- Excuse me.
You want someone
to take the picture?
- Get the fuck off. you little whore.
- What? What?
- Hey. come on. Stand up. yeah.
- What?
- I'm sorry! No. Jack!
- I got you.
- It's all right.
- Oh. my God!
- No. no. it's all right.
- Why did I...
I'm fine. honestly. I'm okay.
This is so stupid.
No. you gotta get ahead
of the swelling.
Just try to find some...
This is so embarrassing.
Here we go.
Yeah. put that on there.
Gotta wrap something up
with it. Find it.
- You like Cheetos?
- No. like gauze.
- Some gauze or something.
- Gauze?
Try to do that.
With that hand.
And do that hand.
You play piano?
Yeah. we gotta
take care of this. then.
Oh. okay. Thanks.
And that's it. yeah. No. but
keep that on there. hold on.
Can you do that? Yeah.
Did you get it?
It's already gotten warm.
hasn't it?
- Should we have gotten two?
- It's okay. No. it's okay.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I had to.
That's all right.
It's not really all right.
though.
Have a good one.
Be careful. she'll hit you.
These rings
are gonna get stuck
if you don't take them off.
- Does that hurt?
- Yeah.
- That's okay. though.
- May I?
Yeah.
Safekeeping.
- Put this on there.
- You're a sweetheart.
And we'll just wrap it up.
You'll be good to go.
How the hell do you deal
with that all the time?
- What's that?
- People just
talking to you
like you're not a real person
- or taking your picture.
- Is that too tight?
It's okay. thanks.
- Oh. I hurt you.
- That's fine. it's okay. Ow...
There we go.
Now. you're mobile.
Swing it around.
I look like a pirate.
Right? I told you
it was worth coming here.
How do you do that?
- Do what?
- Don't change the subject.
Is that what I'm doing?
Nobody ever asked you
about you. huh?
- Not sure.
- Where are you from?
Arizona.
- Arizona boy.
- Mmm-hmm.
Dad had a midlife crisis.
I think.
So I've been told.
Made his way to Arizona.
started working
for this family
on a pecan ranch.
- A pecan ranch?
- Yeah.
Knocked up
the family's daughter.
She was just shy of 18.
Uh-oh.
That's when
I came into the picture.
Okay.
The son of an 18-year-old.
Yeah.
Well. she died at childbirth.
- Then. my dad...
- I'm sorry.
He. uh...
He died when I was 13.
so I guess my brother would
tell you that he raised me.
but I don't know. I don't know
who was raising who.
Just 127 acres of nuts.
Navajo. and nowhere to go.
♪ Tell me something. boy
♪ Aren't you tired.
trying to fill that void
♪ Or do you need more
♪ Ain't it hard.
keeping it so hardcore ♪
Is that me?
That's you.
- Did you just write that now?
- Yeah.
It's pretty good.
♪ I'm falling
♪ In all the good times
I find myself
♪ Longing for change ♪
I started writing this song
the other day.
and maybe that could work.
like as a chorus or something.
I have to think
if I can remember it. Uh...
♪ I'm off the deep end
♪ Watch as I dive in
♪ I never meet the ground
♪ Crash through the surface
♪ Where they can't hurt us
♪ We're far from
the shallow now ♪
Holy shit.
What is this?
Was this supposed to help me?
Can I tell you a secret?
I think
you might be a songwriter.
But don't worry.
I won't tell anybody.
But I'm not very good
at keeping secrets.
You're a real gentleman.
I think.
Thank you. sir.
It's right here. on the right.
- Right there?
- Which one?
- This one.
- Oh. yeah.
What's all this?
Oh. it's my dad.
It's a long story.
What's he. a sheikh?
No. he's a driver.
Hey. I got a gig.
You wanna come?
When?
We're headed
to the airport now.
- Tonight.
- Tonight? No. I can't.
I gotta go to work later.
I gotta go to bed.
Who's gonna take care of your
hand? I messed it up. or...
- Me.
- No. no!
- I'll take care of my hand.
- It's my fault.
- I took you to that place.
- That's okay.
No. listen. Hey!
- You have my number.
- Okay. All right.
Hey.
What?
I just wanted to take
another look at you.
Oh. maybe I fucked that up.
No.
- Hi. Dad.
- Pretty late. pretty late.
- Oh. is it late?
- Yeah.
Look at you. you don't even
know where you're walking.
- Come on.
- Well. I wanna go to bed.
No. come in for two minutes.
It's Wolfie's birthday.
come on!
- Two minutes!
- Okay.
- Wolfie!
- Yeah. sweetheart?
Who was the guy in the car?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Hey. Ally.
- How's it goin'?
- Happy birthday.
- Hey. "happy birthday"?
- Yeah.
- It's not my birthday.
What do you mean?
- Come on.
- No. I was just saying...
What the hell happened
in here? My God!
This place is a mess!
Starting gate
is Shipazo Gito
and bad beat is Wario Peito.
What's going on?
You leave the butter out.
Who the hell's
betting on horses
- at breakfast time in Japan?
- It's not
- breakfast time in Japan.
- They're loading!
- Joe. we're going. Come on!
- You guys are crazy!
Have a sizable
investment on this thing here.
What did I say about smoking
in this house?
- Outside!
- Who are you?
Who am I?
It's my house.
I know it's your house.
But you smoke too.
- All right. forget it.
- Okay. good.
Sweetheart. you're happy here.
aren't you?
I'm happy. Dad.
I'm just saying.
she's got no space.
- What are you saying?
- Wait a minute. sweetheart.
- I'm saying she's got no space.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
I want my friends
to look at you.
Take a good look.
With a voice like from heaven.
but you know what?
It's not always the best
singers that make it.
You know?
I knew a couple of guys
could sing Sinatra
under the table.
But Frank. he'd come on stage
with the blue eyes.
the sharkskin suit.
the patent leather shoes...
He becomes Frank Sinatra.
And everybody else.
all these other guys
that really got it.
that really have it inside.
just a bunch of nobodies.
Okay. Everybody. let's go.
Time for work.
Unfortunately.
you keep blasting the hearing.
it's not gonna come back.
I think it's time
we reconsider
- the inner monitors.
- Mmm-hmm.
We've talked about
that with Bobby
- a couple of weeks ago.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
If we put the inner moles in.
we can actually use those
to amplify the high
frequencies.
- Yeah. okay. that sounds great.
- Cut down the sound.
- Yeah. you're right. Yeah.
- I'm gonna talk to Bobby.
and we're gonna
get something set up.
Sold. I'm sold.
- All right. Jack.
- Yeah. call Bobby.
Stubborn son of a bitch.
All right. let's get
ready. 1. 2. 3. 4.
♪ Killing me. baby.
with the things you do
♪ You put me in the ground ♪
We're trying...
You gotta put 'em in. man.
I told you.
I can't wear those things.
When I wear 'em.
it's just in my head.
and I need to be here
with everybody else.
The doctor said
it's the only way
to manage this thing. Jack.
You're not gonna
get back what you lost.
It's the only way we can
manage what you still got.
Oh. wow.
I think
we're managing pretty good.
What do you
want me to do?
The door's wide open
if you wanna go.
You know what?
Don't start that shit.
Show a little fucking pride
in what you're doing. buddy.
I just wanna know if she's
on her way or not. that's all.
Who's coming?
What the fuck?
- Who's here?
- I have no idea.
He won't tell me.
- Hi. Ally.
- Hi.
- I'm Phil. We met last night.
- Yeah. I remember.
Jack sent me to pick you up
and take you to the gig.
Oh. my God. Um...
But I gotta work. I can't go.
He's really
looking forward to this.
I really appreciate that.
but. uh...
I can't leave.
so I'll be in my car
right down the street.
Please tell him.
"Thank you. but no thank you."
Okay? Say it just like that.
Wait a minute. Ally.
What're you doing?
The fuck is that shit?
- This is crazy.
- What are you doing?
- This is great.
- What the hell's going on?
Look. a guy like that
invites you to a show...
- It could be a great opportunity.
- Dad. don't start with me.
- Don't start!
- Listen. listen!
Does he know you sing at all?
Did he hear anything from you?
Dad. I gotta go to work.
This could be
the opportunity of a lifetime.
I don't have the same disease
that you have. Dad.
You get around celebrities.
and it's like
they're gonna rub off on you.
What are you talking about?
"Oh. you know who I drove
the other day?"
Why are you talking
about that?
Like magic. now you're famous.
And you're not.
It's not magic. Dad.
Sweetheart.
He's a drunk!
You know all about drunks.
Sweetheart. he's still there.
Yo. so you fucking hit a cop?
Yeah. he was being
an asshole to Jack.
so I fucking popped him
in the face.
Yo. that is so gangster.
So. then we ended up
in a parking lot.
and he was putting peas
around my hand to fix my hand.
And then he was singing.
and I was singing.
I don't know
what the hell's going on.
But now he's got his driver
following me around.
Wait. he's been following you
from your house
all the way to work?
- Yes! It's crazy!
- You're fucking late again.
I'm what?
I said you're late!
Are we doing this?
Hey. Bryan. I'm out.
Find somebody else.
Bryan. I'll be back.
I promise.
- Papo. I promise.
- See ya. I won't.
- Did you see Bryan's face?
- Oh. shit!
Hey. great!
Let's do this.
Let's go.
What are we doing?
You know.
if I didn't know Jack.
I would call you a stalker.
Yeah. sorry about that.
Yes. man!
Lay on that couch right now!
I'm gonna take my shoes off.
- Oh. my God!
- This is nice.
How this shit works?
- They just told you no.
- Oh. okay. I'm so sorry.
Oh. shit!
I could get used to this shit.
You need to date
more rock stars.
baby girl.
you know what I'm saying?
We're not dating.
Hi. Ally. I'm Gail.
- Hi.
Oh. you guys can leave your bags.
We'll grab 'em in a sec.
- Ready?
- Oh. Okay. sure.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Thanks.
Did you have
a good trip?
Yeah.
Passes.
- Oh. thank you.
- Put 'em around your necks.
Ear plugs. You'll need these.
it's loud up there.
Yeah. I got 'em.
We're coming in.
I'm gonna bring you guys
to the side stage.
Whoa!
Guys. guys. guys.
This way. Sorry. wrong way.
- It's all good.
- I'm so sorry.
This place is so big.
I'm just...
Come on this way.
Oh. watch yourself.
You guys good?
Hey. boys.
He's so excited
that you're here.
♪ I told my dyin' daddy
♪ That I had to run away
♪ Looked him
in the eye and said
♪ "There ain't no other way"
♪ So. woman. if I tell you
that I love you. be okay
♪ 'Cause I ain't lyin'
♪ I don't lie
♪ Without an alibi
♪ 'Cause I ain't lyin'
♪ I don't lie
♪ Without an alibi ♪
Thank you very much.
That was great.
There's a friend of mine. who
came a long way to be here.
and she wrote a great song.
and I'd just like her
to sing it.
I think
it's pretty fucking good.
- How are you? You made it!
- I'm good. Hi!
It's so good to see you.
How are you?
It was so good.
Everything all right?
The trip was fine?
- Yeah. yeah.
- Phil was all right?
- Didn't bother you at all?
- Gail was so nice.
So. listen. we're gonna sing
that song. all right?
I did an arrangement.
it was kind of not so great.
but maybe you could
just stick with it.
No. I can't do that.
I'm sorry. No. Jack. please.
Yeah. you're coming.
Here we go.
It's not funny.
Jack. don't fuck around.
All you gotta do is trust me.
That's all you gotta do.
I'm gonna
sing it either way. so...
Steve...
You lost your mind. Okay.
- You have to go sing.
- I'm not going out there. no.
♪ Tell me something. girl
♪ Are you happy
in this modern world
♪ Or do you need more
♪ Is there something else
you're searching for
♪ I'm falling
♪ In all the good times
I find myself longing
♪ For change
♪ And in the bad times.
I fear myself
♪ Tell me something. boy
♪ Aren't you tired.
trying to fill that void
♪ Or do you need more
♪ Ain't it hard.
keeping it so hardcore
♪ I'm falling
♪ In all the good times
I find myself longing
♪ For change
♪ And in the bad times.
I fear myself
♪ I'm off the deep end
Watch as I dive in
♪ I never meet the ground
♪ Crash through the surface
Where they can't hurt us
♪ We're far from
the shallow now
♪ In the shallow
Shallow
♪ We're far from
the shallow now
♪ I'm off the deep end
Watch as I dive in
♪ I never meet the ground
♪ Crash through the surface
Where they can't hurt us
♪ We're far from
the shallow now
♪ In the shallow
Shallow
♪ We're far from
the shallow now ♪
Oh. my God!
- Pretty fucking good. man.
- There's so many people.
Pretty fucking good.
You see. the way
the guitar just started and...
I thought maybe
I set it in the wrong key.
and then the tempo
was too fast.
No. it was
so beautiful. and...
I wasn't sure...
- Ally. you okay?
- Jack?
Jack?
You. you. move!
Isn't that the girl who sang?
Good concert. man!
Good concert.
Thank you. yeah. Thank you.
- Jackson. I love you. man.
- Thank you.
Hey. Jack. Killed it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hi!
Oh. my God!
Where's my key?
I don't fucking...
Ah. ha. ha. ha!
Oh. fuck!
I'll be right back. okay?
Just give me one second.
Is this the bathroom?
Where's the fucking...
Okay.
Hey.
Jack?
I don't know. wake him up.
I can't wake him up.
He's drunk.
Yes. you can!
Shake your titties in his face
or some shit.
and just fucking...
You know what I'm saying?
Take two shots and...
Thank you so much for your help.
You are so helpful.
Let me know how it goes. baby.
Go home. pal.
He's out.
You think maybe
he drinks a bit much?
Sweetie. you have no idea.
Tell you one thing. though.
He's never brought a girl
onstage before.
And it's been
a long. long time
since he played like that.
Well. that's good to know.
One time.
my brother came home.
I was playing on this upright
we used to
always have in our den.
And I was in my own world.
No one was ever home.
and then he comes home
to take care of my dad.
who was sick.
And he's sittin' there.
and he's looking at me.
I swear to God.
he looked at me
like I was special
or something.
and it just kind
of filled me up.
I should've never
told you that. I don't know.
Why?
'Cause it's embarrassing.
I don't know.
It's so sweet.
'Cause you're nothing like
my brother. let me just say.
Yeah. I don't look
like your brother?
He's a fucking
old man. okay.
My dad had me
when he was 63 years old.
63 years old?
And we have
different mothers. so...
What's that number down here?
That is how many people
looked at it.
Get the fuck out of here.
How do they know
how many people looked at it?
I think it's... They call it
an algorithm. or...
What's an algorithm?
It's like a beat.
- A beat?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Like in music. a beat?
- Yeah.
Yeah. yeah.
I think. I don't know.
- Do you believe this?
- No.
- Wow.
- And you see this?
- Yeah.
- That's how many people have watched.
Yeah. yeah.
we're just telling...
They was telling him.
How the fuck do they do that?
I've watched it
200 times myself.
- I'm 200 of those people.
- Go. Pops.
Oh. jeez!
My God. you're so fast! Jack!
French toast is
gonna come out.
First one to hit the bed.
♪ I like for you
to let me sing along
♪ Give you a rhythm you feel ♪
Beautiful.
you wrote this with him?
He's so talented.
- Can I watch it again?
- Yeah. it's good.
- Just one more time.
- One more time.
- I'll be up all night watching this.
- Or 500. Come on!
Christ!
♪ I want to play the part
to reach your heart
♪ Sing you a song
that you feel
♪ Oh
♪ Love let your music
be mine...
Oh. my God.
How did you get in here?
Dad let me in.
♪ Let your melodies
fly in my direction
♪ Take me to your paradise
♪ On a musical ride
♪ I'm in love
with your music baby
What?
♪ You're music to my eyes ♪
I don't feel
this way about everybody.
Well. good.
Then we're on the same page.
You come and sing with me.
Where?
Well. first stop's Arizona.
I'm never getting on that thing
with you when you've been drinking.
I haven't even thought about
drinking or anything else.
We'll see how long that lasts.
Go wait downstairs.
Actually. when I was
in my 20's and 30's.
I was like a crooner.
As a matter of fact.
a lot of people thought I was
better than Sinatra.
Frank? Frank Sinatra?
What are you
writing down in here?
That's my songbook.
I usually use a typewriter.
but I had this idea
on the bike
and I didn't wanna forget it.
How do you hear it?
♪ I'm alone in my house ♪
Aren't you excited to be home
and play for
all your Arizonian fans?
I don't really come back here.
You avoid your home?
I don't know.
It's like the hot air
and the history. I don't know.
Bought the ranch. though.
I grew up on.
gave it to my brother.
We buried Dad there. and so
I just wanted to make sure
that nobody paved
over his grave
- or any of that kind of shit.
- Is it around here?
It's not far.
Why don't we just go there?
It's nearby.
Jack?
Yeah. if he shows up.
These guys have been
vamping out there
for a fucking half an hour.
It's time to fucking get on.
Don't you
get tired of being...
You sold Dad's ranch.
They turned it into
a fucking wind farm!
I bought that for you.
Where's his grave?
He washed away
in a fucking storm.
His grave isn't there anymore.
I told you.
but you were fucking drunk.
You were fucking loaded
and already pissing yourself
a swan song.
Fuck if you shed a tear
for that piece of shit
you idolize for
no goddamn fucking reason.
All Dad ever did for you
was make you
his fucking drinking buddy.
And you'd be right there with
him if he was still alive.
and you fucking know it.
What did you think.
that I was gonna fucking
take care of it
while I'm fucking
cradling your ass
all over the goddamn world.
Yeah.
That's a good excuse.
Raising a little brother.
so you don't have
to deal with the fact
that you were no fucking good.
If I was no good. why'd
you steal my fucking voice?
Huh?
'Cause you had
nothing to fucking say.
You were too proud to sing
any of the songs I ever wrote.
Well. I got something
to say now. pal.
I'm done being
your fucking errand boy.
I quit.
Yeah. my voice
just got up on me
a few months ago and
another shot of steroids
is better safe than sorry.
Thank you for that.
and yeah. we should be good.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Well. let's play.
Uh...
Oh!
♪ Don't ask me 'bout tomorrow
♪ Or tell me 'bout my past
♪ My heart is yours to borrow
Ain't nothing meant to last
♪ I ain't lyin' ♪
♪ Maybe it's time
to let the old ways die
♪ It takes a lot
to change a man
♪ Hell. it takes a lot to try
♪ Maybe it's time
to let the old ways die
♪ Nobody knows
what waits for the dead
♪ Some folks just believe
In the things they've heard
♪ And the things they've read
♪ Nobody knows
what waits for the dead
♪ I'm glad I can't go back
to where I came from
♪ I'm glad those days are gone
Gone for good
♪ But if I could take spirits
♪ From my past
and bring 'em here
♪ You know I would
♪ You know I would ♪
All right.
I got an idea for the end.
- Sorry. sweetie.
- That's okay.
- It's gonna be a little different. we're gonna...
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Where's that joint?
We're just gonna be a little
different for the end. okay?
We're gonna do the encore
and the thing that I said.
- Okay. All right.
- All right?
Come on.
let's go back out and do it.
What?
What are you doing?
Go. go. go.
All right. listen to me.
Here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna do
the song that I said
that I wanted you to do.
remember?
- The one that I love.
- No. No. I'm not.
- Please! Come on.
- No. you're gonna do the one that I love.
- It's gonna be great. come on.
- Come on. Jack.
This is what I said
I always...
You promised me
you were gonna do it.
- I always say...
- I love you.
Always remember us this way.
Everybody.
we're gonna bring out Ally
to bring us home.
and she's gonna sing
an original song.
Thank you.
♪ That Arizona sky
♪ Burning in your eyes
♪ You look at me. and babe.
I wanna catch on fire
♪ It's buried in my soul
♪ Like California gold
♪ You found the light in me
that I couldn't find
♪ So when I'm all choked up
and I can't find the words
♪ Every time we say goodbye
Baby. it hurts
♪ When the sun goes down
and the band won't play
♪ I'll always remember us
this way
♪ Lovers in the night
♪ Poets tryin' to write
♪ We don't know how to rhyme
but damn we try
♪ But all I really know
♪ You're where I wanna go
♪ The part of me that's you
will never die
♪ So when I'm all choked up
and I can't find the words
♪ Every time we say goodbye
Baby. it hurts
♪ When the sun goes down
♪ And the band won't play
♪ I'll always remember us
this way
♪ Oh. yeah
♪ I don't wanna be just
a memory Baby. yeah
♪ So when I'm all choked up
and I can't find the words
♪ Every time we say goodbye
Baby. it hurts
♪ When the sun goes down
and the band won't play
♪ I'll always remember us
this way
♪ Way. yeah
♪ When you look at me
♪ And the whole world fades
♪ I'll always remember us
♪ This way ♪
Ally! Ally! Ally! Ally!
That was fucking beautiful.
No.
you were fucking doing it.
I was there. I fucking...
- I think our car's over there.
- Ally. that was unbelievable.
- Thank you.
- That was unbelievable
- what you did up there.
- Thank you.
I don't know
if you know anything
about me.
about where I've come from.
I'm Rez Gavron.
I know who you are.
What you have right now
goes way beyond just this.
There's people
who need to hear
what you have
to say musically.
This is not normal stuff.
It's really amazing
what you're doing.
I think you have it all. I do.
And the question to you is.
"What do you want?"
I'm in that position. to put
you wherever you want to be.
I don't... I don't have...
I gotta talk to Jack.
He said
he thought Interscope Records
might really wanna sign me.
and he said that he has
this wonderful studio
with a beautiful live room.
And these amazing producers
he wants to bring in
to record my songs.
And he loves
"Look What I've Found."
Remember the song
we did in the diner?
Remember.
when we were driving?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I mean. it was so nice
talking to him.
and he really believes in me.
- You all right. Jack?
- He's okay. He's fine.
He does this all the time.
Hey. Jack.
Thanks.
What's going on?
Hmm?
What're you doing?
You jealous fuck.
I'm so happy for you.
Oh. you are?
Oh! Jackson!
Oh. my God!
Jack. Stop!
Why're you so jealous.
boy? Hmm?
What're you doing?
What's wrong? You upset?
You want me to
make you less...
I know. do you wanna play?
Okay. let's play.
What the hell is this?
- I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
- No. you're fine. You're all fine.
- You sound great. okay?
- You're doing great.
We'll do it again.
I'm gonna cue you in.
- One. two...
- ♪ I'm alone in my house ♪
One second. one second.
Listen to my cue.
We'll come right in. okay?
So. should...
Well. uh...
I'm sorry. but will I
sing in the beginning?
So you're gonna
hear the second line.
and then I wanna
start recording.
I think I got an idea that
might help out. all right?
Yeah. please. Be my guest.
That was really good
up to that point.
- I'm just gonna go in there for a second. all right?
- All right. Jack.
I've never sang
with a track before.
I think it's because
you need your piano.
I think if you're playing it
and singing it...
Yeah. I always play it
on the piano. I'll be fine.
I'm just gonna have them fly
one in. and we'll try it there
- and see where it goes.
- You think that's okay?
Okay. Thank you.
I got you.
You're doing great.
- You okay?
- No. I'm so nervous.
- You look so beautiful.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
♪ I'm alone in my house
♪ I'm out on the town
♪ I'm at the bottom
of the bottle
♪ I've been knocking 'em down
♪ I can't get back up
on my feet
♪ See the lights on the street
Like stars
♪ But look what I found ♪
Oh. so you guys have already
met the new girl. have you?
- Rez! What's the plan?
- What's up?
Yo. thanks for doing this.
man. I appreciate it.
This is pop music. kids.
We have a battle to do. okay?
You are the troops.
so if I call you troops.
just know that
we're going into battle.
What is my lyrics. Ally?
♪ Just don't keep me waiting
Yes! Again. give me that.
♪ When I can't inspire myself
- Breathe! Yes!
- ♪ I need you to provide for me ♪
This is just fine-tuning
and creating an image.
I know.
I just don't wanna lose
the part of me
that's talented.
I'm not gonna let you
lose that piece.
Okay.
What are we gonna do with you?
What are we gonna do with...
Oh. he's beautiful!
"You can't send me back.
I'm too cute."
- Hey. he's got your eyelashes.
- Mmm-hmm.
He does. He's got
your eyelashes. Hey. bud!
This has never been done
before. just so you know.
It actually has
been done before.
Would you please...
Please. Do it for me.
No. I can't in the water.
You comin' with me to Memphis?
- What are you talkin' about?
- I gotta go do this. um...
You know.
it's one of those paid things.
Soul-crushing work. really.
but it's just kind of never
what I thought
I'd wind up doing. maybe.
I don't know. but...
I've made peace with it.
though.
Anyway. if you wanna come.
I thought
we'd have a laugh.
at the very least.
Rez wants to
keep me here because.
you know.
they rushed out the single.
and they were so excited
that they want me to
finish the album.
- So I'm working on that.
- Listen to what you're saying.
Listen to what you just said.
People wanna hear
what you have to say.
- That's the stuff right there.
- I know. I can't...
Hey. hey. Take it in.
Thank you. by the way.
Thank you for what?
Giving me a home.
This place never
felt like one before.
Oh. fuck.
Jack. you okay?
Jack?
♪ Treat me like your patient
♪ Just don't keep me waiting
♪ Or I'll just be wasted
in a crowd of the lonely
♪ I need you to inspire me
♪ When I can't inspire myself
♪ I need you to provide for me
Is there a reason
why you're not up there?
♪ Lay me down
Lay me down now
Touch my spirit. oh
♪ Lay me down
Lay me down now
♪ Heal me
♪ God knows
nothing else is gonna
♪ Gonna heal me
♪ Oh. before it's too late
Won't you steal me
♪ Steal me
all the way from myself
♪ Won't you heal me
Oh. my God! Oh. my God!
Oh. my... Oh. my... Hey!
- Pretty incredible.
- Did Jack show up?
I haven't heard from him.
What do you mean.
you haven't heard from him?
I haven't heard
from him all night.
I haven't been able to find him.
I called him three times.
Listen. what happened
with the dancers there?
Well. I just thought
that I should do it alone
'cause it's so overwhelming.
Okay. but you can't
go rogue on me.
You have to understand
that this is what I do.
and you have to
trust me. okay?
So. if I give you
a couple of dancers.
don't not use them and then
miss a couple of steps. okay?
We also have to
change your hair.
We have to
change the color of your hair.
What's wrong with my hair?
I'm thinking platinum. or...
I don't wanna be
fucking blond.
I am who I am.
and I'm worried about Jack.
I will find Jack. okay?
I will find him.
Jack.
I feel like
we've done this before.
Didn't think
we'd do it so soon. man.
Come on. bro. Get up.
All right. There we go.
In my mind.
I made it to the door.
I almost didn't wake you.
You looked so comfortable.
How you doin'?
You know. I've seen
better days. I guess.
I apologize for
disrespecting your property...
No apologies necessary.
...or whatever I did.
- It's fine.
- You want some coffee?
Be great.
why don't you put some on.
and we'll come in in a minute?
Okay.
That's him. right?
That's your boy.
Jack. he's as old now
as you were when I met you.
Saw you on YouTube.
- That video with the girl.
- Yeah.
It made me happy. man.
You looked like you.
You were just...
Just doing it. bro.
She writes too.
- She wrote that tune?
- Yeah.
Bunch of others too.
Got hooked up with some
manager guy. wants to...
Yeah.
- She's good. bro.
- I know.
Maybe she's a way out.
Ain't nothing to
be afraid of. bro.
You know. it's like...
I don't know...
You float out...
Float out at sea. and then
one day. you find a port.
Say. "I'm gonna stay here
for a few days."
A few days
becomes a few years.
And then you forgot where you
were goin' in the first place.
And then you realize.
you don't really
give a shit about
where you was going
'cause you like
where you're at.
That's how it is for me.
I like where I'm at.
I didn't even realize
I liked it so much
till I saw your ass sleeping
in the grass this morning.
Yeah. come on. man.
You can rest
in my daughter's room. bro.
I thought of a million things
to say to you on the plane
that I can't remember.
Jack...
Glad you're here.
You did make it
to Memphis after all.
Fuck.
I won't do this again.
I won't come and find you.
Next time. you can clean up
your own mess.
You understand me?
How was the show?
It was fucking awesome.
I cut the dancers.
Dancers?
Yeah.
Oh.
Good.
Fucking dancers.
All you do is you just sing.
You made me so upset.
I'm sorry.
- I saw that video on YouTube.
- Oh!
It was great.
Thank you so much.
Excuse me one second.
- What's going on?
- Do you have a plier?
Jack's okay?
I wanna cut the guitar
strings. not too crazy.
There used to be pliers
or something like that.
Uh... Yeah. yeah.
I don't know
where my mom is.
- Yeah. I understand that.
- I think you're pretty.
Me?
You think I'm pretty?
Thank you.
I think you're pretty.
It was real great.
and then
Jack tells me
you wrote the song.
Yeah.
he got me to start singing
my own songs again.
He has a way of doing that.
Yeah. he does.
Does anyone want some
more mac and cheese?
Yeah? Here. sweetheart.
you want some?
Oh. there he goes.
What's up. man?
I understand what you said.
What the hell are you...
Are you kidding?
- That stupid?
- No. It's not stupid.
It wasn't a stupid thing
I just did?
Is that what you were doing
when you left the table?
I don't know. He told me he
was looking for some pliers.
I didn't know
what he was going to do.
I didn't think
he was gonna "do it" do it.
Oh. she has another ring!
Well. that's just temporary.
No. no. no.
Jack. wait a minute.
Let's anoint this.
Let's do it today.
- Yo. for real.
- It's a good idea!
No. you get the dress.
I'll call my cousin right now.
It's Saturday.
Nobody's gonna be in there.
- Let's go.
- You really wanna do that?
That place has
a magical quality to it.
It what?
It has a magical quality?
- It does.
- What do you mean?
- I mean that church is special.
- We can go.
- I'll take you to get a dress.
- There you go. right there.
It'd be great!
Okay. you're coming
with us for sure
because you're...
I can't believe this.
What am I doing? Okay. sure.
♪ I don't know
what love is... ♪
- My brother. Good to see you.
- Hey. hey!
- Good to see you. Jack!
- Good to see you. my man.
Thank you so much.
Welcome to the Lord's house.
With the power...
I think that's how it goes.
something like that.
Do you take him...
Do you take him?
I do.
♪ I think that it's just fear
♪ I don't know the tempo... ♪
Congrats. man.
- I listened to what you said.
- I'm glad you did.
I can't believe he did it.
I can't believe it.
Now. one thing at a time.
okay?
What?
Oh!
I didn't understand.
♪ It's not
♪ I know there's something
real out there for me
♪ I swear I've seen an angel ♪
- Lot of people downstairs?
- Yeah.
She better come out soon.
- before they leave.
- Want me to check on her?
Well. I think we're gonna have
to go pretty soon. so...
All right.
Ally.
I'm coming in.
What're you doin' in the tub?
This is so weird.
I don't know
who the hell I think I am.
One song is fine.
but to put out a whole record.
I don't know
what the fuck I was thinking.
about all of that.
but you definitely
look like a star.
- Really?
- Yeah.
What do you think of her hair
and the look and the...
- Well. I discussed it with her.
- Yeah.
- No. I think it looks great.
- Was that your choice. or...
No. it was actually hers.
- No drink?
- What's that?
No drink?
No socks?
Touche. Touche. mate.
Yeah. I could never
get used to that.
the idea of not wearing socks.
Your feet get all...
No. actually
I'm wearing socks.
They're these kind of
little female insert socks
that work with these shoes.
Oh. you are.
You're just hiding them.
Yeah. I'm just hiding them.
That's right.
Okay. now is this thing...
Yeah. there it is.
Oh. that's a good light.
Here. hold this for me. baby.
Hey. Ally. girl!
Wait. hold on. Come here.
Sooki. Donte. Come here.
I put my Jackson titties on!
Hi!
Baby. listen. we just wanted
to say congratulations.
- Congratulations!
- We love you!
I love you too.
All right. girl.
please come back soon.
We done put Etta
in your station. girl.
- The queen is here!
- Stop!
- Wow!
- What do you think?
Well. it's beautiful.
You. SNL.
Alec Baldwin hosting.
- Did you get it? Did you get it?
- Season finale.
- No fucking way.
- No. you got it.
- No way! Oh. my God!
Oh. gosh!
- That's incredible! Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Bitch!
- Oh. my gosh!
- We have to get downstairs.
- Everyone's waiting for you. Come.
- Okay.
You know what? Can I just
talk to her for one second outside?
Just one sec. sorry.
Just be a second. yeah.
It doesn't do you any justice.
I'll tell you that.
You always said
you liked my nose.
- I love your nose.
- It's real big up there.
I wish it was bigger up there.
The whole thing
should just be
your fucking nose.
Fuck all those people
who ever said anything.
Just put a billboard
of your fucking nose up there.
Just the nose?
That's so ridiculous.
Listen.
if I just don't say this.
I'll never forgive myself.
What?
If you don't dig deep
in your fucking soul.
you won't have legs.
I'm just telling you that.
You don't tell the truth
out there. you're fucked.
All you got is you. and what
you wanna say to people.
and they are
listening right now.
and they're not gonna
be listening forever.
Trust me.
So. you gotta grab it.
And you don't apologize.
you don't worry about
why they're listening.
or how long they're gonna
be listening for.
you just tell 'em
what you wanna say.
'Cause how you say it
is the stuff of angels.
Pop! Six to the right.
and hot!
Ball. change. Down.
Hot! Ball. change.
Attitude.
- The last part.
- I know.
30 seconds.
Red mark.
Alec in 20.
15.
All right. stand by. guys.
Here we go. ready? Song one.
- Stand by. Alec.
- In 10. 9...
- Alec in 10.
- ...8. 7. 6...
- Ready 4...
Alec in 5 seconds.
4. 3. 2. 1...
And go 4.
Dissolve 4.
- and cue Alec!
- Ladies and gentlemen...
- Ally.
- Dissolve 1.
♪ Why do you
look so good in those jeans
♪ Why'd you come around me
with an ass like that
♪ You're making
all my thoughts obscene
♪ This is not. not like me
♪ Why you keep on
texting me like that
♪ Got other things
I need my mind on. yeah
♪ Other responsibilities
♪ This is not. not like me
♪ Why do you do that
♪ Do that do that
do that do that
♪ Do that to me
♪ Why do you do that Do that
do that do that do that
♪ Do that to me
♪ Why do you do that
♪ Do that do that
do that do that
♪ Do that to me
♪ Why do you do that
♪ Why do you do that ♪
The caterpillar
becomes the butterfly.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm in town for a gig.
Been working for Willie.
- I've been working for Willie.
- No shit.
Yeah. Thought I'd stop by
and check her out.
- Yeah. well...
- ♪ I've been praying on my knees
♪ That you would
always stay around
♪ That you would never leave ♪
Is it gettin' worse?
Nah. I've just been
with my wife.
and it's goin' real good.
Funny to run into you
'cause I was thinking
about asking you
to come back out with us.
I gotta say.
it's easier without you.
Listen.
You run into any trouble.
call me.
♪ Why do you do that
♪ Do that do that
do that do that
♪ Do that to me
♪ Why did you do that to me
♪ Why did you do that ♪
Thank you!
♪ I don't wanna
feel another thing
feel another thing ♪
That light's beautiful.
Oh. God. here we...
Yeah. that's it. Ally.
Yeah. that's it.
That's it. Ally.
That's it. I love that.
Oh. my gosh. It's so early.
I've been here all night.
It's early for me.
It's late for you.
Hi. it's nice to see you.
- How you doin'?
- I'm kind of...
- He's amazing. Isn't he?
- What do you think?
These fucking photos.
- Oh. they're so beautiful.
- Look at that! Look at that!
That's incredible.
It doesn't even look like me.
You've just been nominated
for three Grammys.
Including "Best New Artist."
They just announced it now.
Everybody.
Grammy-nominated artist.
Have you been drinking?
Are you fucked up right now?
I'm out a couple.
It's the morning.
Yup.
Hey. buddy.
You're nominated
for three Grammys.
and it's fucking great.
Thank you.
How did you find that out?
Bobby told me.
He called. He said that
they wanna do
some Roy Orbison tribute.
They want me to sing and shit.
- Great.
- Some like supergroup thing.
But the point is. you got
nominated. and it's great.
I'm just trying to
figure it out. that's all.
"Why do you come around me
with an ass like that?"
You're saying my lyrics?
"Why do you walk around
in jeans?"
"Why do you wanna come around
with an ass like that?"
Yeah. that's my song.
What about my song?
I fucking listened to it over
and over in the fucking...
You're not making any sense.
Yeah. just keep drinking.
That'll give you the answer.
Maybe I just fucking
failed you.
- That just kills me. I'm sorry.
- You what?
You failed me?
Yeah. you're embarrassing.
and it's just...
- I'm embarrassing?
- I feel bad for you.
- Yeah. I just... You know...
- I'm not fucking embarrassing!
- I just have to tell you.
- You're embarrassing!
And you know
what you're doing is
you're so embarrassed
of your fucking self
that you gotta put me down.
You're worried that you're ugly. and
you're not. I'm trying to tell you that.
So you need to
get all this fucking approval
by all these other people.
Why can't I just
be enough for you?
I don't need approval.
You know what I'd like is
for my boyfriend to love me.
Actually. for my husband
to love me.
Yeah. who's
your fucking boyfriend?
- You have a boyfriend?
- Yeah. I've got a boyfriend.
- That hurts.
- Yeah. I have a boyfriend.
Call me
your fucking boyfriend.
You're my boyfriend.
You're my boyfriend if you
don't treat me like your wife.
I don't even know
what that fucking means.
It means clean your shit up.
You're fucking messy.
- That's what it means.
- Well. that's not true.
- Oh. it isn't?
- Mmm-mmm.
Let's go. You wanna
be my drinking buddy?
Wanna practice?
I don't think
you could handle it.
You don't? Let me see.
And you know why? 'Cause
you're too worried about what
- everybody else is thinking.
- Here we go.
Here we go. Jack.
You want me to be your dad?
- Be your drinking buddy?
- Yeah.
Yeah. you couldn't be my dad
if you fucking tried.
He had more talent
in his fucking finger
than you have in
your whole fucking body.
So don't even fucking go there
about that. all right?
That's over the fucking line.
Why don't you
have another drink.
and we can just
get fucking drunk
until we fucking
disappear. okay?
Hey! Do you got those pills
in your pocket?
You're just fucking ugly.
that's all.
- I'm what?
- You're just fucking ugly.
Get the fuck out.
Get out!
I said. get out!
Fine.
Good evening.
Down!
7 and 8 and...
2. 3. 4. 5. 6. 7...
Pull it!
6... Come on. feel it...
Hit! Down. up! High! Swing it!
Six... Come on! Yes!
♪ Tryin' to leave you
♪ But you won't let me leave.
sayin' that about me
♪ Got me thinkin'
I'll never succeed
Hold the music!
- That was great.
- What are you doin' here?
Something fell through.
so I was able
to come back a few days early.
I think I might
have said some things...
Just how I acted.
You hurt me.
You really hurt me.
Sorry.
You haven't been drinking.
What'd you say?
I said you haven't been
drinking. I can tell.
No. I haven't. No.
I have to get back
to rehearsal...
Oh. yeah.
Can I watch?
Yeah. okay.
Meet me at home.
Or I can wait
and drive you home.
- Just meet me at home.
- Okay.
What do you mean.
they don't want me to sing?
They hired this fucking kid
at the last minute.
They didn't tell me
a fucking thing.
Look. we've been
on that other side before.
More than once.
Yeah.
Truth is. I didn't deliver.
Well. it's a good thing
I know the. uh...
How to play the
guitar. It's fine. I'll do it.
- You're gonna do it?
- Sure.
♪ I couldn't help but see
♪ Pretty woman
Hey. where's the wedges?
Can't fucking hear with the...
- Is the monitor here?
- ♪ Are you lonely just like me
- ♪ Pretty woman. walk a while
- All right.
♪ Pretty woman. talk a while
♪ Pretty woman.
give your smile to me
yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
But yeah. like I said.
it's a real honor.
Yeah. Oh. honor's mine.
Yeah. you're great.
It'll be fun.
- Yeah. hope so.
- Yeah.
Who coulda been a crooner?
Right?
You remember what Paul said.
"Paul Anka told me
I had more natural talent...
- "...than Sinatra."
- "...than Frank."
- That's it! Do not...
- Direct quote!
Do you know what Paul
Anka actually said to him?
- No. what did he say?
- He said.
"Would you please
pull the car over
"and let me out
over here on the curb?"
All right. but...
Oh. my God!
Sweetheart.
This is unreal.
The Grammys.
Hey. look at everybody.
How are you?
Hey. there he is!
- Oh. thanks.
- How are you?
Are you okay?
- What's that?
- Are you okay?
Are you okay?
- Oh. yeah. I'm great.
- Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm great.
They have me going in early.
so I gotta go now and then...
But I made sure that they
tell me where you're sitting.
so that I can go right after.
- Okay. Okay.
- 'Cause I don't wanna miss
the awards
because it's right before it.
- Looks great.
- You just got that look on your face.
I do? Watch... It's gone.
Amazing. Gonna get to see
you perform tonight.
get to see you sing.
Hey. Jack. that's an
incredible collection of vinyl
you have in there.
Take whatever you want.
It's yours.
Take whatever I want?
He just said.
"Take whatever you want."
He's talking to
the wrong guys.
♪ Pretty woman
♪ Walkin' down the street
Pretty woman
♪ The kind I'd like to meet
I thought he was
supposed to be singing.
♪ I don't believe you
You're not the truth
♪ No one could look
as good as you ♪
Oh. God!
- ♪ Pretty woman
- ♪ Won't you pardon me
♪ Pretty woman
I couldn't help but see
♪ That you look lovely
as can be
♪ Are you lonely
just like me ♪
Oh. it's over? It's over?
- You good?
- I'm fine.
And the nominees are...
- Right here?
- Roxy Carlile.
Come on. baby.
Sit down. sit down. sit down.
Hi. You okay?
I was trying to
go to the men's room.
- and they rushed me over here.
- Okay. put your legs inside.
- I had to go to the bathroom.
- Put your legs inside.
They're announcing your
fucking category. Keep quiet.
- And the winner is...
- Yeah...
Oh. this is exciting.
How great.
Ally!
Oh. my God! Oh. my God!
Oh. my God!
This is amazing!
All right.
What happened?
Baby... We won!
- Is that why everybody's...
- Yep. that's right!
Yeah. Ally!
Where are we going?
Just stay right here.
Go sit back there.
I'll stay here.
Oh. my gosh. thank you!
You look beautiful. Thank you!
Oh. wow!
Oh. my gosh!
I can't believe
I'm holding one of these.
Thank you to Rez Gavron.
my manager.
Thank you for
believing in me...
Wait. did you win?
...and telling me to
get back from
behind the piano
and onto the stage.
Did you just win?
Thank you to my... My. uh...
To Jack Maine. my husband.
- Should I come up there?
- I love you so much.
I always wanted to be a singer
on a big stage.
and because of him. I am.
We're having
a lot of fun tonight.
Yeah.
- I...
- Shit.
Look.
If I haven't thanked you
yet. just...
Did you see you're up there?
Yeah. I do.
I started out singing
with this beautiful man.
and I'll sing with him
for life. Right. baby?
Yeah.
I'm so blessed to be
in the company
of such wonderful musicians.
This is a dream come true.
and all I can say is...
...believe in yourself.
and don't give up
because there is a spot
on that stage for you.
- Oh. shit. Oh. fuck.
- Good night.
- I think I peed myself.
- Baby. just turn around.
Oh!
- I think I do...
- Baby. baby. can you...
- I think that's a bad come down.
- Holy shit!
- Just take him to the shower. Go to the left.
- Follow me. Wolf.
Ally. you just go
inside. okay?
- It's on the left. Dad.
- I got it.
- Go inside!
- They got him.
- they got him. They got him!
- It's my job!
Don't you fucking
do this to my daughter.
Hey. hey!
What the fuck is
wrong with you?
Get off!
Damn it!
Watch his fucking head.
What. what?
Bobby'll take you there.
You have Bobby's number?
No. Jack. hon.
you gotta sit up.
I don't want you to choke.
baby. Sit up!
All right.
I might've taken too much.
You all right in there?
I'm fine.
He's fine.
So.
everybody has their journal.
and we remember
the homework assignment.
the three things that
I wanted you to write down.
Jack. hey.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I'm late.
You can't be late. Jack.
Understood. sorry.
Good. where's your journal?
- It's in my room.
- No. no. no.
Sit down.
So. it's all agreed. Nobody's
ever late here. right?
Okay. Good.
Anything you wanna tell us?
Um...
I'm grateful to...
To be here
and trying to
hold it together.
I'm Jack. I'm an alcoholic.
Jack.
Drug addict.
This is all my fault.
You don't have
that kind of power. Dad.
Eat your dinner.
Eat your food.
I don't even know
what meal it is.
Go and have some fruit.
How many times did you carry
my piano up the stairs?
How many times did you sit
there while I wrote a song?
- Always.
- Okay. it's okay. It's okay.
You didn't do anything.
It's not your fault.
You're just the greatest
person in the world.
How long have you
been here now?
Two months.
Can it be fixed?
Well. you would know that.
don't you?
Once it's gone. it's gone.
I don't know what you have.
Oh. well. the tinnitus.
they say. once you...
- Oh. tinnitus can't be fixed.
- Right.
Well. I just hear that tone.
that's all.
The tone. yeah.
The ringing.
I have hearing aids on.
as you...
No. I know.
That's why I asked you.
You know. I'm convinced that
it happened when I
was younger. I used to...
My dad had a Victrola.
an old record player.
My head was just about the
size of it when I was a kid.
and I used to love to just
put my whole head in there.
He was big into
the blues. so...
'Cause you gotta figure. it's
just me and him all day long.
My brother's out there tryin'
to make something of himself.
So I took one of his belts.
I put it around
the ceiling fan
and tried to do the deed.
The whole fucking fan
came out of the ceiling.
Had a big cut
on my fucking forehead.
I was more mad about that
than it not working.
And he didn't even notice.
He didn't even fucking notice.
- 'Cause he was drunk?
- Yeah.
That fucking fan stayed on the
floor for about half a year.
How old were you then?
I was just shy of 13.
Aww!
You smell good.
and you look good too.
Swimming. I've been swimming.
- You've been swimming?
- Yeah. there's a pool.
- I love that you're swimming.
- Yeah.
- That's a great pool there.
How's Charlie?
Oh. Charlie's sweet.
He just sort of sits
by the door like this.
Waiting for daddy.
We're both waiting for daddy.
What. three weeks?
You are gonna
come back. right?
What do you mean?
You gonna come home
when you're done?
- Do you not want me to?
- No. I want you to.
I'm just wondering if...
I just...
- Where else would I go?
- I don't know.
I guess I just thought...
You know. it's like...
- There's Jack...
- Wait. wait. wait.
- Why would you say that?
- I don't know. I guess...
I wondered. without the booze.
if you would want
to come home.
'Cause when you met me.
you were drinking.
and now you're not.
I wasn't drunk the whole time
we were together.
I know. but...
But it got bad
when we were together.
It's okay. I mean. it's fine.
I just was wondering.
that's all.
and whatever you want is okay.
Whatever I want?
I wanna be with you.
- That's why I'm here.
- Okay. I know. I know.
I just want you to be happy.
I'm working on that.
I need to stick with you.
I brought something.
I wanna know
what this is.
"My Love."
You hiding love songs?
No. I wouldn't...
I wouldn't say
I was hiding it. I just...
I started puttin' it
down to paper
when we were at home.
I don't know. it just
sort of fell out of me.
I guess. and onto this page.
And I put it in here.
and I thought...
I thought
maybe you'd find it
when you came
back to you. maybe.
Well. I found it.
Listen.
I'm. uh...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I...
It's not your fault.
I'm sorry I did that.
It's okay.
It's not your fault.
It's a disease.
No. but I embarrassed you.
- I embarrassed you. and I...
- I'm not embarrassed of you.
It was so wrong.
And then your dad...
My father loves you.
it's okay.
I know. but I...
- It's okay.
- I know. but I...
It's okay.
I have figured out
what I think is
the best solution
for both of us.
Jack should come out
on tour with me.
We'll start with our duets.
I know he's gonna be able
to play by himself.
You realize
that's not an option.
He's so inside of his art
in a way he has never been.
- He can hear himself again.
- Ally. there is no way
that you can take Jack on tour
with you. There is no way.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
You know what? If you can't
make that happen.
then fucking cancel the tour.
I don't know what to tell you.
I think if we had
a better band name.
we might've made it.
Or maybe it was 'cause
we looked like
a father and son duo.
Not many of those around.
I was not a good look for you.
that's for sure.
Not my fault I couldn't find
a better guitar player
in the whole goddamn state.
Where in the fuck is it?
Right here.
Thanks for the ride.
Sure thing. Jack.
Hey. you know. uh...
When I. um...
When I said I would...
You know. when I...
Took your voice. you know.
It's you
I idolized. It wasn't Dad.
What was that guy?
Hey.
I wanna know
how you hear this.
That sounded unbelievable.
what you were playing.
- Thank you.
- It's nice to hear it.
Thank you. and I had
the beautiful backdrop
of you and Charlie.
I only heard it in my mind for
so many weeks.
so it's good to hear it...
The words are beautiful.
In the real thing.
- Well. you want me to do that?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh. God. I don't know.
I knew you were gonna ask me.
Back from the dead.
Hey. sorry.
Were you waiting long?
Hey. Jack. No. no.
Uh... Ally's not home.
No. I told her I'd meet her
here. if that's okay.
Of course. yeah.
Here you go.
Hey. thanks for taking care of
my girl when I was gone.
Anything for her.
She told me about
that European leg.
That's a hell
of an accomplishment
this soon out of the gate.
Shit. I remember
it was like ten years
before I even went
across the pond.
It was summer. 2004.
Shit. was it?
We're not exactly
friends here.
While you've been away.
we've been back here
in serious triage.
trying to clean up
your fucking mess.
Barely finding
our way through it.
You almost single-handedly
derailed her whole career.
You understand that?
She's never gonna
say this to you.
She loves you too much.
Just by staying married to
you. she looks like a joke.
It's embarrassing.
Let's be honest. we both know
it's only a matter of time
before that's pushed aside
again for the real thing.
And when that happens.
I don't want her
anywhere near you.
Hey.
I have some good news.
- Yeah?
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm not gonna go to Europe.
We're gonna cancel
the rest of the tour.
and I'm just gonna
be here all summer.
Isn't that great?
What happened?
Nothing happened.
The label just
loves the record.
and it's doing so well.
and they wanna keep
with the momentum
and have me make another one.
Rez is super psyched.
so it'll be great.
So tonight's
gonna be my last show.
Going out with
a bang at the Forum.
Great.
Yeah.
Why don't you come with me?
We can sing "Shallow"
together.
The fans will go crazy
to see you.
Come on. cowboy.
Yeah. why not? Okay.
Yeah?
Okay. good.
I'll have a car come get you.
Once I get there.
I'll go meet you there.
I'll see you soon. okay?
Hey.
What?
I just wanted to take
another look at you.
Bye. honey.
Bye.
Come here. Charlie.
Come here.
Thank you so much for
bringing us all here together.
Please look over all of the
dancers tonight and the band.
And my husband. Jackson.
We're so excited for him
to be here with us.
We got a big night.
We're at the Forum. LA.
Let's do this.
♪ Why did you do that? ♪
Is he here?
He's not here.
He's not here?
We have to do "Shallow"
regardless. okay?
The guitar's up there.
Everything's gonna
remain the same. okay?
- What?
- The guitar's up there.
Everything's gonna
remain the same.
Both verses.
I'm sure it was just a bit
much for him. that's all.
Please send somebody
to the house. please.
I'm doing it right now.
I have 15 seconds.
♪ In the shallow
♪ We're far from
the shallow now ♪
Give it up for my husband.
Jackson.
I can stay. if you want.
Some kid started
singing one of his songs
in a bar I was
in the other night.
They're playing
his songs everywhere.
At first I got angry.
I don't know why.
I guess I felt like.
how can any of these people
feel like they knew him?
Who he really was.
But then something changed.
And it soothed me.
That it wasn't
all for fucking nothing.
The last thing
I did was lie to him.
Listen to me.
It isn't your fault.
It just isn't.
You know whose fault it was?
Jack.
That's it.
No one else.
Not you. not me.
No one but Jack.
I just keep
going over and over it.
over it in my head.
Jack talked about how music is
essentially 12 notes
between any octave.
12 notes
and the octave repeats.
It's the same story.
Told over and over.
Forever.
All any artist
can offer the world
is how they see
those 12 notes.
That's it.
He loved how you see them.
He just kept saying.
"I love how she sees them.
Bobby."
Hello. I'm Ally Maine.
Thank you for
being here tonight
to honor my husband.
He wrote a song for me.
I'd like to sing it
for him tonight.
And with your help.
maybe I can.
Thank you.
Really.
♪ Wish I could
♪ I could've said goodbye
♪ I would've said
what I wanted to
♪ Maybe even cried for you
♪ If I knew
♪ It would be the last time
♪ I would've broke
my heart in two
♪ Trying to save a part of you
♪ Don't wanna feel
another touch
♪ Don't wanna start
another fire
♪ Don't wanna know
another kiss
♪ No other name
falling off my lips
♪ Don't wanna give
my heart away
♪ To another stranger
♪ Or let another day begin
♪ Won't even let
the sunlight in
♪ No. I'll never love
♪ Again
♪ I'll never love again
♪ When we first met
♪ I never thought
that I would fall
that I'd find myself
♪ Lying in your arms
♪ And I wanna pretend
that it's not true
♪ Oh. baby. that you're gone
♪ 'Cause my world
keeps turning
♪ And turning and turning
♪ But I'm not moving on
♪ Don't wanna feel
another touch
♪ Don't wanna start
another fire
♪ Don't wanna know
another kiss
♪ No other name
falling off my lips
♪ Don't wanna give
my heart away
♪ To another stranger
♪ Or let another day begin
♪ Won't even let
the sunlight in
♪ No. I'll never love
♪ I don't wanna
know this feeling
♪ Unless it's you and me
♪ I don't wanna waste a moment
♪ And I don't wanna
give somebody else
♪ The better part of me
♪ I would rather wait for you
♪ Don't wanna feel
another touch
♪ Don't wanna start
another fire
♪ Don't wanna know
another kiss
♪ Baby.
unless they are your lips
♪ Don't wanna give
my heart away
♪ To another stranger
♪ Don't let another day begin
♪ Won't let the sunlight in
♪ Oh. I'll never love again
♪ Never love again
♪ Oh. I'll
♪ Never
♪ Love again ♪
♪ Life is so simple
♪ A little boy a little girl
♪ Laughing and loving
♪ Tryin' to figure out
the world
♪ It felt like summer
When I kissed you in the rain
♪ Oh. I know your story
But tell me again
♪ Nothing you say
wouldn't interest me
♪ All of your words
are like poems to me
♪ I would be honored
if you would take me as I am
♪ I want you
♪ To look right in my eyes
♪ To tell me you love me
♪ To be by my side
♪ I want you
♪ At the end of my life
♪ I wanna see your face
♪ When I fall with grace
♪ At the moment I die
♪ Is that all right?
♪ Is that
♪ all right? ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Sync by GoldenBeard
♪ Black eyes open wide
♪ It's time to testify
♪ There's no room for lies
♪ And everyone's
waiting for you
♪ And I'm gone
sitting by the phone
♪ And I'm all alone
by the wayside
♪ And I'm gone
sitting by the phone
♪ And I'm all alone
by the wayside
♪ And I'm gone
sitting by the phone
♪ And I'm all alone
♪ And I'm off alone
by the wayside
♪ By the wayside
♪ Black eyes open wide
♪ It's time to testify
♪ There's no room for lies
♪ And everyone's
waiting for you
♪ Everyone's waiting for you
♪ Oh ♪
♪ That Arizona sky
♪ Burnin' in your eyes
♪ You look at me and babe
I wanna catch on fire
♪ It's buried in my soul
♪ Like California gold
♪ You found the light in me
that I couldn't find
♪ So when I'm all choked up
and I can't find the words
♪ Dreams of you and me
are in the dirt
♪ When the sun goes down
♪ And the band won't play
♪ I'll always remember us
this way ♪